Steven Gozali

IT Operations / IT Developer

Having a year of experience in maintaining the availability of the application and work closely with the vendor for a banking company. Involved in developing 3 projects for solving/improving client's business process. Feel free to visit my portfolio

WORK EXPERIENCE

IT Operations

July 2022 - Present

PT. Bank Mestika Dharma, Medan, Indonesia

- Queries using SQL server and Oracle regarding abnormal transaction or providing reports that other division's needs
- Maintains web servers (Apache) and deploys updates of application
- Backup and housekeeping logs in CentOS 7 and Solaris server using cronjob
- Uses **JIRA** for ticketing and **Trello** for managing work loads.

Sales Officer April 2021 - July 2022

PT. Karsa PrimaPermata Nusa. Medan. Indonesia

English Teacher

January 2018 - April 2021

International Education Centre, Medan, Indonesia

PROJECTS EXPERIENCE

Cashflow Management System (implements Virtual Account)

Cinta Budaya School, Medan, Indonesia

July 2022 - present

- * RestAPI (ExpressJS) that enables VA provider (BCA) to inquiry data or to notice our system if there is a payment occurs. Database used is MariaDB
- Desktop App (C#) to manage the system, such as issuing bills to students, handling scholarship, and much more scenario.
- * Web Application (NextJS) to enable students doing online books purchase. The payment is integrated to the Virtual Account.
- Configuring web server (NGINX), domain and SSL installation. In addition, install neccesary apps, such as pm2 and MariaDB and manage its backup using cron.

Member Mobile Application

PT. Supernet Nusantara, Medan, Indonesia

August 2022 - January 2023

- Mobile App (React Native) for building features are such as checking the members' point/downline, registering a new member using QR Code and online product purchases.
- RestAPI (ExpressJS) to fetch data from Microsoft SQL Server.
- Firebase for OTP and authentication.
- **Deployment** to the Play Store and App Store.

Online Stock Management (implements multiple eCommerce API) May 2023 - August 2023 ledsmarthome, Jakarta, Indonesia

RestAPI (Spring Boot - MVC pattern) to connect multiple shops in multiple ecommerces. The RestAPI will fuse the API from multiple e-commerces into single

- Web App (NextJS) to manage shops, such as orders, products, logistics, and other modules.
- Deploys and maintains a VPS (Linux CentOS 8) which consists of the application and MongoDB to support the application.

CONTACT



Medan, ID (opens to other cities)



+62 853 6163 6260



stevengoh.work@gmail.com



stevengoh.vercel.app



github.com/stevengoh29

SKILLS

Frontend:

- React Js
- React Native
- NextJS

Backend:

- NodeJS
- ExpressJS
- C#
- Spring Boot

Database:

- MySQL/MariaDB
- Microsoft SQL Server
- MongoDB

Others:

- Firebase
- Linux Server
- C# Windows Forms

EDUCATION

Mikroskil University

Computer Information Systems Medan, ID (2019 - 2023)

Awards:

1st rank of Business Apllication Competition in 2021 (C# Winforms and Ms SQL)

1st rank of Web Application Competition in 2022 (React, Express, and MySQL)

Cinta Budaya School

Science Major Medan, ID (2017 - 2019)